So now the fun really starts to begin with the accessories.
And that's where you can add your prints in.
Because remember, we started our capsule we were all solids.
So now you want to add the prints to give that little bit of pizzazz to your wardrobe.
I love to do that with scarves.
Especially, like a Chanel scarf.
It's classic.
It goes on forever.
You never will be outdated in a Chanel scarf.
Or any actually designer scarves.
I love the prints of scarves and they really can bring out your fashion personality.
So if you like something a little bit more flamboyant or you're more classic.
I always tell my clients, if they are a scarf wearer, to pick up a scarf when they're traveling.
European women wouldn't be caught dead wearing anything but a beautiful scarf when they go out and anytime of really any time of the day or night.
So, when you're traveling in Europe, or any of your travels, picking up a scarf is always a wonderful conversation piece to.
You go to a party or a networking event and not know anybody.
Wear a fabulous scarf or a piece of jewelry that's very interesting and - let me tell you - people start coming up to you and start talking to you.
And all your fears about being the only one there that you know - yourself - they all go away.
Because you will have something to talk about.